Tucson at the Millennium photograph Collection, 1999-2000 MS458
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Tucson at the Millennium photograph collection1999-2000
MS 458
Tucson at the Millennium Committee
16 Linear Feet
This collection is made up of photographs taken in the years 1999 and 2000. The bulk of the collection is from 1999. The collection gives a historical view of Tucson at the edge of the Millennium. The photos were taken by amateurs, professionals, and people from all walks of life. They capture individual visions of what embodied Tucson in 1999. The majority of photographs are color or black-and-white prints and range in size from 4” x 6” to 16” x 20”. Many are matted and some are framed.
Main Library Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
None
Historical Note
Tucson at the Millennium was a photographic celebration of Tucson sponsored by the Tucson Museum of Art, The Tucson Citizen, and Research Corporation. Those involved in the planning were John Schaefer of Research Corp., Don Hatfield of the Citizen, Robert Yassin, director of the Tucson Museum of Art, Harold Jones, Ann Simmons Myers, and Jack Dykinga to name a few. Participants were encouraged to submit photographs that embodied Tucson as it entered the 21st Century. People submitted as many entries as they wanted as long as they met the criteria. All entries were received by December 31st, 1999.
Selected images were published in the Tucson Citizen or on their website with the individual photographer credited. When the project was completed, 100 photos were selected that best represented Tucson. These were displayed at a special exhibit at the Tucson Museum of Art and published in book form which was marketed to the public. Hundreds of other selected images were also displayed at satellite shows around Tucson at the Center of Creative Photography, Tucson High School, Pima Community College West Campus, and Tohono Chul Park.
The entire collection has become a visual archive housed at the Special Collections, Main Library University of Arizona.
Series List
Series I: Documentation, 1999-2000
Series II: Photographs, 1999-2000
Subseries 1: Prints, 9x12 inch
Subseries 2: Box, 12x15 inch
Subseries 3: Box, 17x21 inch
Subseries 4: Box, 17x23 inch
Subseries 5: Box, 26x33 inch
Subseries 6: Framed prints
Box 16: 12x15 inch
Box 17-18: 21x25 inch
Box 19-20: 23x31 inch
The bulk of the collection contains photographs, some on mat board and some in frames. Also included is a small amount of correspondence and other business related materials for Tucson at the Millennium. Photography includes images that reflect the social, cultural, and commercial facets of the community as well as landscapes and sunsets in Tucson, Arizona between 1999- 2000. The documentation series includes files on the selection of images for the exhibit at the Tucson Museum of Art, the book, and the digital collection/IPTC created by the Tucson Citizen. The photograph series includes images submitted for the Tucson at the Millennium contest. The images are arranged by size and organized alphabetically by photographer’s last name. The majority of prints include identifying numbers created by the committee.
Photography – Arizona – Tucson– Exhibitions.; Photography – Arizona – Tucson – Pictorial works.; Artists – Arizona – Tucson – Exhibitions.; Architecture– Arizona – Tucson – Pictorial works; Street signs in art; Signs and signboards – Arizona – Tucson – Pictorial works; Landscapes -- Arizona -- Tucson Region – Pictorial Works; Cactus -- Arizona – Tucson – Pictorial Works; Human beings in art; Tucson (Ariz.) – Pictorial works
- Series I: Documentation, 1999-2000
  This series is arranged alphabetically. It contains correspondences, budget information for the project and the copy images for the different exhibitions, published book and from the Tucson Citizen digital collection.
  - Book images: Tucson at the Millennium, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Exhibition images for CCP, PCC, SP, Tohono Chul, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Exhibition images for TMA, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Images from Tucson Citizen Digital Collection, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Images from Tucson Citizen Digital Collection, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Images from Tucson Citizen Digital Collection, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Images inventory for TMA (floppy drive and a paper of the inventory) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Information: Mailing list, list of photographs, budget and time line for the contest, meeting minutes, flyer advertising contest, and newspaper article about the “Tucson at the Millennium” exhibit, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Series II: Photographs, 1999-2000
  This series is arranged alphabetically by artists’ last name. For the same artist, the photos are arranged by the unique number originally assigned as photos were received. This series contains 5 subseries. The first subseries include two boxes which are classified by envelope size, and the rest of subseries are arranged by the Box size.
  - Subseries 1: Prints, 9x12 inch
    - Allen, Sammie #331 (Box 2, 1)
    - Alvarez, Freddy #157-162, 387-393 (Box 2, 2)
    - Angel, Debbie #1075, 1084 (Box 2, 3)
    - Armas, Nancy #489-490 (Box 2, 4)
    - Arriola, Joseph #649, 652 (Box 2, 5)
    - Ashford, Sarah L. #396 (Box 2, 6)
    - Ashley, Geoffrey H. #734, 1181 (Box 2, 7)
    - Auerbach, Gary # 118-119, 522-525 (Box 2, 8)
    - Ault, Matt #488, 567 (Box 2, 9)
    - Baker, Tina #1076-1080 (Box 2, 10)
    - Barrett, V. William #541-554 (Box 2, 11)
    - Beauchamp, Jennifer #1024 (Box 2, 12)
    - Benally, Dezbah #939 (Box 2, 13)
    - Bermudez, Joni and Anthony #279-286 (Box 2, 14)
    - Bermudez, Joni C. #456-460 (Box 2, 15)
    - Bialopiotrowicz, Catherine #779-794+1 Print without # (Box 2, 16)
    - Bilski, Andre J. #165-166 (Box 2, 17)
    - Bondante, Chris #735-737 (Box 2, 18)
    - Boyce, Martha #473-474 (Box 2, 19)
    - Brown, Lorlei #421-423 (Box 2, 20)
    - Brown, Val #432 (Box 2, 21)
    - Browning, Linda #198-200 (Box 2, 22)
    - Buckholz, Jessica #857-858 (Box 2, 23)
    - Buckner, Ellen #408-410 (Box 2, 24)
    - Buffenmyer, Marie #433-436 (Box 2, 25)
    - Bumham, Laurel #856 (Box 2, 26)
    - Campbell, Robert #750-766, 1124 (Box 2, 27)
    - Cathers, Cliff #289-292 (Box 2, 28)
    - Cid, Marcela Ines #553 (Box 2, 29)
    - Cinquemani, Peter, Jr. #186-195 (Box 2, 30)
    - Clark, Juliana #847-849 (Box 2, 31)
    - Close, Alice #327 (Box 2, 32)
    - Clouse, Don #747 (Box 2, 33)
    - Clute-Ruddick, Bonnie #1089-1090 (Box 2, 34)
    - Condon, Steven J. #239 (Box 2, 35)
    - Conway, April #860-861 (Box 2, 36)
    - Cosentino, Nancy #1085-1086 + 1 Print without # (Box 2, 37)
    - Cosgrove, Elizabeth #974-987 (Box 2, 38)
    - Crane, J. W. #540 (Box 2, 39)
    - Crescenzi, Christine #377-378, 381, 384 (Box 2, 40)
    - Croyle, Edwin #1027 (Box 2, 41)
    - Cruz, Jose Ramon #357-368 (Box 2, 42)
    - Cuffe, Elaine #103 (Box 2, 43)
    - Cuffe, Scott #1-3 (Box 2, 44)
    - Cunningham, Dianne #151-156, 293-297 (Box 2, 45)
    - Curtis, Shirley #237 (Box 2, 46)
    - Cutler, Natalie M. #229-231 (Box 2, 47)
    - Cutshaw, Cari #863 (Box 2, 48)
    - Danby, David #446-554 #863 (Box 2, 49)
    - DarConte, Lorraine A. #471, 480, 673-674 (Box 2, 50)
    - David, Brandon #996-997 (Box 2, 51)
    - Denfeld, Mic #954-956, 1109 (Box 2, 52)
    - Deeter, April #661-662 (Box 2, 53)
    - Delaney, Jane #315 (Box 2, 54)
    - deSimone, Diane #545-547 (Box 2, 55)
    - DeWitt, Ronald L. #1017-1019 (Box 2, 56)
    - Diemer II, Michael #1049-1054 (Box 2, 57)
    - Dolny, Carmen #1025-1026 (Box 2, 58)
    - Drew, Lindy #1184 (Box 2, 59)
    - Eddy, Kenna #559-561 (Box 2, 60)
    - Eldridge, Eleanore #429-431 (Box 2, 61)
    - Etsitty, Jennifer #913-919 (Box 2, 62)
    - Ey III, John A. #892-896 + 1 Print without # (Box 2, 63)
    - Field, Jenny #1011-1012 (Box 2, 64)
    - Fein, Samantha #852-853 (Box 2, 65)
    - Ferrell, Gloria Montejo #97-102, 142-146, 202-217, 256 623-624, 1110-1123, 1262-1268, 1285-1290 (Box 2, 66)
    - Fine, Loretta Mae #225 (Box 2, 67)
    - Fly, Henry N. #1081-1082 (Box 2, 68)
    - Foreman, Travis C. #238 (Box 2, 69)
    - Furr, Lee #910-911 (Box 2, 70)
    - Gibbs, Paula #476-478 (Box 2, 71)
    - Glickman, Eileen #554 (Box 2, 72)
    - Gottlieb, Hildy #998 (Box 2, 73)
    - Gould, Pam #11 (Box 2, 74)
    - Graham, Adam #644-648 (Box 2, 75)
    - Gray, Dave “Frosty” #83-84, 164, 271 (Box 2, 76)
    - Grimes, Patrick #28-31, 33-35, 37-41 (Box 2, 77)
    - Grugutis, Morgan #850 (Box 2, 78)
    - Guggi, Jessica #851 (Box 2, 79)
    - Hackney, Edere Hart #469 (Box 2, 80)
    - Hannan, Dolores #85-86 (Box 2, 81)
    - Hannigan, Norah #221-222 (Box 2, 82)
    - Hanon, Dee #402-404 (Box 2, 83)
    - Haynes, Susan #437-438 (Box 2, 84)
    - Helfrich, Morgan #854 (Box 2, 85)
    - Helms, Lucille #467 (Box 2, 86)
    - Herman, Casia #843 (Box 2, 87)
    - Hotz, Frank #1261 (Box 2, 88)
    - Hood, Fred #584-602, 605-608 (Box 2, 89)
    - Howell, Robert #399-401 (Box 2, 90)
    - Illig, Deborah #122 (Box 2, 91)
    - Jackson, Nicolas #862 (Box 2, 92)
    - Jackson, Thelma R. #461 (Box 2, 93)
    - Jenkins, Toni #317-323 (Box 2, 94)
    - Jenks, Stu #520-521 (Box 2, 95)
    - Johnson, Charles #563-564 (Box 2, 96)
    - Johnson, Danette #548-550 (Box 2, 97)
    - Joslyn, Carolyn #924-926, 1253 (Box 2, 98)
    - Juliano, Cindy #385 (Box 2, 99)
    - Kennedy, Dale #663-666 (Box 2, 100)
    - Kilpatrick, Brian #953 (Box 2, 101)
    - Kincaid, Khela #470-471 (Box 2, 102)
    - Kingery, Korey #748-749 (Box 2, 104)
    - Knauff, Meg #1040-1048 (Box 2, 105)
    - Knight, David #946-952 (Box 2, 106)
    - Kornylak, Andrew #966 (Box 2, 107)
    - Koss, Richard E. #220 (Box 2, 108)
    - Lamantia, Sarah #859 (Box 2, 109)
    - Leacock, Betsy #247-254, 1031-1039 (Box 2, 110)
    - Lee, Deborah A. #324-325 (Box 2, 111)
    - Lemon, Dot #423-428 (Box 2, 112)
    - Leyva, Rene #841-842 (Box 2, 113)
    - Linderman, Lori #298-314 (Box 2, 114)
    - Lindley, Richard E. #332 (Box 2, 115)
    - Liscum, Bill #485-486 (Box 2, 116)
    - Lochert, Martha #1260 (Box 2, 117)
    - Longcore, Randall #1190-1194, 1195-1198 (Box 2, 118)
    - Lynn-Rivera, Susan #1147-1167 (Box 2, 119)
    - Mackay, Malcolm R. #580-583 (Box 2, 120)
    - Mangels, Pat #468 (Box 2, 121)
    - Martin, Cathy #150 (Box 2, 122)
    - Martin, Glenn #270 (Box 2, 123)
    - Martin, Tom #90-92, 95-96 (Box 2, 124)
    - Massey, M. Jason #491-493, 496-498 (Box 2, 125)
    - Maxton, Robert L. #487 (Box 2, 126)
    - McFadden, Michael D. #653-660+1 Print without # (Box 2, 127)
    - McLaren, Fiona #1220 (Box 2, 128)
    - McMorrow, Heather #694-695, 697 (Box 2, 129)
    - Milender, Shirley #1059 (Box 2, 130)
    - Moffett, Sally #464 (Box 2, 131)
    - Mohnacs, Mary #255, 257-261 (Box 2, 132)
    - Moncrief, Karen #463 (Box 2, 133)
    - Morris, F. Robert #767-778 (Box 2, 134)
    - Morrow, Regina A. #413-414, 422 (Box 2, 135)
    - Mullins, Doug #1055-1056 (Box 2, 136)
    - Myers, Max #1013-1014 (Box 2, 137)
    - Myers, Kathleen #147-148 (Box 2, 138)
    - Nagura, Chihiro #568, 570-579 (Box 2, 139)
    - Naranjo, Ruben Vasquez Jr and Abeyta, Antonio S. #682-685 (Box 2, 140)
    - Nelson, Eylene #462 (Box 2, 141)
    - Nicholas, R. Shirley #397 (Box 2, 142)
    - Noebels, Peter #929-934 (Box 2, 143)
    - Notarnicola, Cathy #733, 898-909 (Box 2, 144)
    - Oberto, Terry #937-938, 945 (Box 2, 145)
    - Ochart, Killi 1 Print without # (Box 2, 146)
    - Ochart, Midge #675-676 (Box 2, 147)
    - Ortiz, Gilbert R. #610 (Box 2, 148)
    - Patterson, Dana #612 (Box 2, 149)
    - Peachin, Mary #4, 123-136, 443-445 (Box 2, 150)
    - Pearce, Wayne #1178-1180 (Box 2, 151)
    - Pena, Gina #219 (Box 2, 152)
    - Persky, Marvin #995 (Box 2, 153)
    - Prater, Shannon #226 (Box 2, 154)
    - Prince, Elizabeth #1022-1023, 1071-1074 (Box 2, 155)
    - Probasco, Opha #333-356 (Box 2, 156)
    - Pryor, Jean E. #1163 (Box 2, 157)
    - Reyes, James O. #562, 677 (Box 2, 158)
    - Richards, Elizabeth #141, 218 (Box 2, 159)
    - Robinson, Kathy L. #5-10, 465-466 (Box 3, 1)
    - Rodney, Steven #472 (Box 3, 2)
    - Rodriguez, Elma #262-264 (Box 3, 3)
    - Rogers, Lenn #398 (Box 3, 4)
    - Ronstadt, James F. #87 (Box 3, 5)
    - Root, William Pitt 1 Print without # (Box 3, 6)
    - Ross, Corene #668 (Box 3, 7)
    - Rubin, Terri + Ben #64-81, 272-278 (Box 3, 8)
    - Russell, Beth McCullough #628-636 (Box 3, 9)
    - Ryan, Nancy #12-27 (Box 3, 10)
    - Sadowsky, Cindy #328 (Box 3, 11)
    - Sagi, Guy J. #197, 501-506 (Box 3, 12)
    - Salonia, Rosanna #738-742+1 Print without # (Box 3, 13)
    - Sanchez, Marisabel #927-928 (Box 3, 14)
    - Savore, Brian #855 (Box 3, 15)
    - Schachter, Josh #994 (Box 3, 16)
    - Schapp, Joan-Anne #967 (Box 3, 17)
    - Schnauss, Jerold W. #743-746, 1070 + 1 Print without # (Box 3, 18)
    - Schreiner, Mary Amy #330 (Box 3, 19)
    - Schumacher, Roger #499 (Box 3, 20)
    - Scott, Harrison #171-177, 405, 551-552 (Box 3, 21)
    - Senn, F. Scott #287-288 (Box 3, 22)
    - Sheley, Alice #137-139 (Box 3, 23)
    - Short, Ray #643 (Box 3, 24)
    - Simmons, Gorden #988-991 (Box 3, 25)
    - Simpson, Peggy #415 (Box 3, 26)
    - Snow, Esther #507-515 (Box 3, 27)
    - Sooy, Carrie #960-965 (Box 3, 28)
    - Stephenson, Donna #1083 (Box 3, 29)
    - Stone, Luke #89 (Box 3, 30)
    - Stone, Ronda #527-531 (Box 3, 31)
    - Stump, Jo Ann #245-246 (Box 3, 32)
    - Swenson, Diana #104, 416-420 (Box 3, 33)
    - Teiwes, Helga #1269-1284 (Box 3, 34)
    - Terrazas, Jane Conklin #993 (Box 3, 35)
    - Thompson, Paul #326 (Box 3, 36)
    - Tiller, Frank #795-810, 811-825, 826-839 (Box 3, 37)
    - Traver, David #844-846 (Box 3, 38)
    - Traver, Roy W. #920-923 (Box 3, 39)
    - Trombetta, Lena #935-936 (Box 3, 40)
    - Unangst, Jacgueline #170 (Box 3, 41)
    - Utter, Aida #500 (Box 3, 42)
    - Valdez, Carol #266 (Box 3, 43)
    - Valencia, Angela #265 (Box 3, 44)
    - Van Valkinburgh, Cassy #1058 (Box 3, 45)
    - Vanderford, Rachel #178-185 (Box 3, 46)
    - Vasquez, Roman #316 (Box 3, 47)
    - Vergason, Jon #1020 (Box 3, 48)
    - Walker, Kimberly #556-557 (Box 3, 49)
    - Warner, Amelia #1029-1030 (Box 3, 50)
    - Weiskotten, Thomas #1015-1016, 1057a+b + 2 Prints without # (Box 3, 51)
    - Whitley, Patty #482-484 (Box 3, 52)
    - Wick, Thersa #626-627 (Box 3, 53)
    - Wieczorek, Elizabeth A. #106-115 (Box 3, 54)
    - Wight, Dianne #1060-1069 (Box 3, 55)
    - Wilde, Kathryn #999-1010 (Box 3, 56)
    - Williams, Owen #866, 868-973 (Box 3, 57)
    - Williams, Susan #693 (Box 3, 58)
    - Wintz, Edward Randall #167, 169 (Box 3, 59)
    - Wood, Shandiin #940, 944 (Box 3, 60)
    - Zak, Barry #82, 121 (Box 3, 61)
    - Zygmon, Bryan #149 (Box 3, 62)
  - Subseries 2: Box, 12x15 inch
    - Almodova, Mark #1102 (Box 4, 1)
    - Arriola, Joseph #650-651 (Box 4, 2)
    - Ashley, Geoffrey #1182-1183 (Box 4, 3)
    - Auerbach, Gary #117, 232-235 (Box 4, 4)
    - Bialopiotrowicz, Catherine #722 + 1 Print without # (Box 4, 5)
    - BonDante, Chris 1 Print without # (Box 4, 6)
    - Buckner, Ellen #407 (Box 4, 7)
    - Campbell, Robert #1092, 1135-1142 (Box 4, 8)
    - Clouse, Don #12, 1215-1216 (Box 4, 9)
    - Crescenzi, Christine #379 (Box 4, 10)
    - Darconte, Lorraine #479, 669-670, 672 (Box 4, 11)
    - Drew, Lindy #1185-1188 (Box 4, 12)
    - Doucette, Sheryl #53-56, 59-61, 63 (Box 4, 13)
    - Estrada, Jessica #1172, 1176 (Box 4, 14)
    - Ferrell, Gloria Montejo #44-45, 47-50, 1125-1127 (Box 5, 1)
    - Glickman, Eileen #555 (Box 5, 2)
    - Gold, Marcia #372-373 (Box 5, 3)
    - Grimes, Patrick #32 (Box 5, 4)
    - Herman, Casia #726 (Box 5, 5)
    - Hymer-Thompson, Karen #8, 638 (Box 5, 6)
    - Kilpatrick, Brian #1189 (Box 5, 7)
    - Krackel, Tye #120 (Box 5, 8)
    - La Prise, Sandra #1131-1134 (Box 5, 9)
    - Lesch, Willaim #1256 (Box 5, 10)
    - Longcore, Randall #1199-1211 (Box 6, 1)
    - Lynn-Rivera, Susan #1143-1146, 1163 (Box 6, 2)
    - Maxwell, Harold #386 (Box 6, 3)
    - McLaren, Fiona #1221, 1222-132, 1236-137 (Box 6, 4)
    - McMorrow, Heather #698-699 (Box 6, 5)
    - Miller, Nicole 1 Print without # (Box 7, 1)
    - Moffet, James #455 (Box 7, 2)
    - Moreno, Jessica #618-621 (Box 7, 3)
    - Moreno, Terrsa Engle #439 (Box 7, 4)
    - Morrow, Regine #412 (Box 7, 5)
    - Mozitis, Ron #1130, 1245 (Box 7, 6)
    - Nagura, Chihiro #569 (Box 7, 7)
    - Noebels, Peter #1169 (Box 7, 8)
    - Notarnicola, Cathy 1 Print without # (Box 7, 9)
    - Oppenheimer, Shirley #1214 + 1 Print without # (Box 7, 10)
    - Oroz, Isabel S. #1128-1129 + 1 Print without # (Box 7, 11)
    - Richards, Elizabeth #1244 (Box 7, 12)
    - Root, William Pitt #702 (Box 7, 13)
    - Russell, Beth McCullough #912 (Box 7, 14)
    - Salonia, Rosanna #719 + 1 Print without # (Box 7, 15)
    - Schreiber, J Keith #1257 (Box 8, 1)
    - Shilkitus, Diane #201 (Box 8, 2)
    - Sims, Lyn #680 (Box 8, 3)
    - Smith, Misti #1217-1219 (Box 8, 4)
    - Sooy, Carrie #1254 (Box 8, 5)
    - Stephenson, Donna #1177 (Box 8, 6)
    - Stone, Rhonda #532-535 (Box 8, 7)
    - Tiller, Frank #99, 721-722, 1248 + 1 Print without # (Box 8, 8)
    - Traver, Ray W. #1170 (Box 8, 9)
    - Walker, Kimberly #558 (Box 8, 10)
    - Wallingford, Ward #536-537 (Box 8, 11)
    - Weiskotter, Thomas R. #1091 (Box 8, 12)
    - Wick, Theresa B. #625 (Box 8, 13)
    - Wilde, Katherine 2 Prints without #’s (Box 8, 14)
    - Wintz, Edward Randall #168 (Box 8, 15)
    - Wright, Karen #613-614, 617 (Box 8, 16)
    - Ziemer, Judith #690 (Box 8, 17)
  - Subseries 3: Box, 17x21 inch, (Prints inside are 14x18 inch)
    - Crescenzi, Christine #376, 380, 382 (Box 9, 1)
    - Gold, Marcia #369-371, 374 (Box 9, 2)
    - Grossman, Herbert #688 (Box 9, 3)
    - Hymer-Thompson, Karen #639-640, 642 (Box 9, 4)
    - Maratea, Anthoney (Jony) #329 (Box 9, 5)
    - Notarnicola, Cathy #704 (Box 9, 6)
    - Sawyer, Mark #441-442 (Box 9, 7)
    - Schreiber, J Keith #706 (Box 9, 8)
    - Sobina, Rosanna #703 (Box 9, 9)
    - Stulac, David #1258-1259 (Box 9, 10)
    - Tiller, Frank #705 (Box 9, 11)
    - Wieczorek, Elizabeth #105, 108 (Box 9, 12)
    - Aguirre, Jame #196 (Box 10, 1)
    - Alvarez, Freddy #394-395 (Box 10, 2)
    - Auerbach, Gary #117, 235 (Box 10, 3)
    - Bialopiotrowicz, Catherine #873-874 (Box 10, 4)
    - Bondante, Chris #1093 (Box 10, 5)
    - Brown, Lorelei (Mrs.) #5 (Box 10, 6)
    - Canade, Ruth #667 (Box 10, 7)
    - Hammett, Ron #406 (Box 10, 8)
    - Clark, Juliana #871, 1094 (Box 10, 9)
    - Crescenzi, Christine #375, 382 (Box 10, 10)
    - Damavandi, Nina #1108 (Box 10, 11)
    - Doucette, Sheryl #52, 57, 62 (Box 10, 12)
    - Drew, Lindy #870 (Box 10, 13)
    - Engie, Burt #440 (Box 10, 14)
    - Estrada, Jessica #1101, 1104-1105 (Box 10, 15)
    - Ferrell, Gloria Montejo #42-43, 46 (Box 11, 1)
    - Grimes, Patrick #36 (Box 11, 2)
    - Grossman, Herbert #686, 687 (Box 11, 3)
    - Jenks, Stu #516-518, 521 (Box 11, 4)
    - Johnson, Charles #565-566 (Box 11, 5)
    - Kingery, Karey #877, 878 (Box 11, 6)
    - Lesch, William #707, 942-943 (Box 11, 7)
    - Lochert, Martha #868-869 (Box 11, 8)
    - Longcore, Randall #883 (Box 11, 9)
    - Lynn-Rivera, Susan #1100, 1249-1250 + 1 Print without # (Box 11, 10)
    - Madden, Laura #622 (Box 11, 11)
    - Martin, Tom #93-94 (Box 11, 12)
    - Massey, M. Jason #494-495 (Box 11, 13)
    - McLane, Claire #872 (Box 12, 1)
    - McLaren, Fiona #884, 1238-1243 (Box 12, 2)
    - McMorrow, Heather #696, 700 (Box 12, 3)
    - Miller, Nicole #1095 (Box 12, 4)
    - Naranjo, Ruben Vasquez, Jr. #681 (Box 12, 5)
    - Nielsen, Erwin “Bud” #888-889, 1213 (Box 12, 6)
    - Noebels, Peter #1099 (Box 12, 7)
    - Notarnicola, Cathy #864-865 (Box 12, 8)
    - Oroz, Isabel #885 (Box 12, 9)
    - Ortiz, Gilbert #609, 611 (Box 12, 10)
    - Pearce, Wayne #1103 (Box 12, 11)
    - Petty, Allyson #1251-1252 (Box 12, 12)
    - Prater, Shannon #227-228 (Box 12, 13)
    - Probasco, Opha #338 (Box 12, 14)
    - Richards, Elizabeth #887 (Box 13, 1)
    - Robinson, Ed #88 (Box 13, 2)
    - Salornia, Rosanna #1096 (Box 13, 3)
    - Sanches, Maisabel #1098 (Box 13, 4)
    - Schrieiba, J. Keith #1107 (Box 13, 5)
    - Sims, Lyn #678-679 (Box 13, 6)
    - Smith, Jay W., Dr. #267-269 (Box 13, 7)
    - Snow, Esther #909 (Box 13, 8)
    - Stephehenon, Donna 1 Print without # (Box 13, 9)
    - Stulac, David #1255 (Box 13, 10)
    - Telwes, Helga #875-876+1 Print without # (Box 13, 11)
    - Thompson, Karen Hyner #641 (Box 13, 12)
    - Tiller, Frank #1246-1247 (Box 13, 13)
    - Traver, David #882 (Box 13, 14)
  - Subseries 4: Box: 17x23 inch, (prints inside are 16x20 inch)
    - Traver, Roy #879 (Box 14, 1)
    - Trombetta, Lena #1097 (Box 14, 2)
    - Utter, Aida #500 (Box 14, 3)
    - Wiewandt, Thomas #1212 (Box 14, 4)
    - Williams, Owen #867 (Box 14, 5)
    - Wright, Karen #615-616 (Box 14, 6)
    - Ziemer, Judith #691-692 (Box 14, 7)
    - Zuckerman-Brown, Amy #539 (Box 14, 8)
  - Subseries 5: Box, 26x33 inchs, (includes some prints 21x25 inchs)
    - Auerbach, Gary #526 + 1 Print without # (Box 15 (In oversize), 1)
    - Bruwer, Andre #881 (Box 15, 2)
    - Budnik, Dan #1106 (Box 15, 3)
    - Gargasz, Norma Jean 2 Prints without # (Box 15, 4)
    - Grossman, Herbert #689 (Box 15, 5)
    - Heisey, Adriel #897, 941 + 1 Print without # (Box 15, 6)
    - Kramer, Denise #1171 + 1 Print without # (Box 15, 7)
    - McLaren, Fiona #886 (Box 15, 8)
    - Medina, Francisco 1 Print without # (Box 15, 9)
    - Schrieiba, J. Keith #880+1 print without # (Box 15, 10)
    - Stulac, David #708, 890-891 + 1 Print without # (Box 15, 11)
  - Subseries 6: Framed Prints
    - Teiwes, Helga / 6th street, bus stop, 12x15inch (Box 16, 1)
    - Auerbach, Gary / B-29 Hanger 4 at the Pima Air Space Museum, 21x25 inch (Box 17, 1)
    - Estrada, Jessica / Mass on Native American Day, 21x25 inch (Box 17, 2)
    - Cramer, Denise / Tucson Mountains, 21x25 inch (Box 17, 3)
    - Lesch, William / Gilamon Saguaro hand weld, 21x25 inch (Box 18, 1)
    - Lynn-Rivera, Susan / Yamela at San Xavier graveyard, 21x25 inch (Box 18, 2)
    - Nielsen, Erwin / Saguaro National Park, Tucson, 21x25 inch (Box 18, 3)
    - Gaynor, Gary / Millennium, 23x31 inch (Box 19, 1)
    - Helsey, Adriel / Archaeological excavation before, 23x31 inch (Box 19, 2)
    - Helsey, Adriel / Home adjoining Saguaro Natl. Park, 23x31 inch (Box 19, 3)
    - 23x31 inch (Box 20)
    - Kramer, Denise / Untitled, 23x31 inch (Box 20, 1)
    - Schreiber, Keith / Southeast Corner of 4th Ave. and 9th Str, 23x31 inch (Box 20, 2)
    - Stulac, David / Captured Saguaros, 23x31 inch (Box 20, 3)
    - Weis, P.K. / Millennium view, 23x31 inch (Box 20, 4)
  - Subseries 7:Tohono Chul Exhibition
    - Campbell, Robert #717, Knight, David #725 (Box 21, 1)
    - Peachin, Mary #475, Ruddick-Clute, Bonnie; Hood, Fred #603 (Box 21, 2)
    - Joseph, Sharen Lee #713, Cosentino, Nancy #711-712 (Box 21, 3)
    - Teiwes, Helga #724 (Box 21, 4)
    - Gallegos, Xavier #728, Canez, Val #727 (Box 21, 5)
    - Wallingford, Ward Without # (Box 21, 6)
    - Simmons, Gordon #714, Weiskotten, Thomas R.#710; Hood, Fred #604 (Box 21, 7)
    - Ferrell, Gloria Montejo #715, Teiwes, Helga #723 (Box 21, 8)
    - Campbell, Robert #716, Whitley, Patty #481 (Box 21, 9)
    - McLaren, Fiona #731 (Box 21, 10)
    - Estrada, Jessica #729 (Box 21, 11)
    - Doucette, Sheryl #58 (Box 21, 12)
    - Ferrell, Gloria Montejo #51 (Box 21, 13)
  - Subseries 8: Miscellaneous
    - Bondante,.Chris. The Great Ones, 20x20 inches, 1987, Heisey, Adriel Houses in the Mountains, 20x26 inches (correct color balance) undated (Box 22, 1, 2)